{
    "subject": "resource/Silapathar",
    "predicate": "property/areaCode",
    "object": "+91, 03753",
    "human_readable": "Silapathar's area code is +91, 03753.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8472265005111694,
            "question": "What is the area code for Silapathar?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.71522456407547,
            "question": "What is the numerical representation of the Silapathar area code?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7088702917098999,
            "question": "What are the two formats of the Silapathar area code?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.383611798286438,
            "question": "Is there a specific prefix needed to make international calls from Silapathar?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.34288954734802246,
            "question": "If you want to call someone in Silapathar from another country, what would you dial first?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3313373029232025,
            "question": "What is the significance of an area code?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3243907392024994,
            "question": "Which country does the +91 prefix belong to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.32026612758636475,
            "question": "How can you dial a number in Silapathar from within India?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.23376253247261047,
            "question": "Can you give examples of other Indian cities and their area codes?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.22415053844451904,
            "question": "How can knowing the area code be helpful when making phone calls?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Silapathar's area code is +91, 03753.",
            "html": "dbpedia_690_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you give examples of other Indian cities and their area codes?",
            "html": "dbpedia_690_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How can you dial a number in Silapathar from within India?",
            "html": "dbpedia_690_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Which country does the +91 prefix belong to?",
            "html": "dbpedia_690_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_690_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_690_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_690_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_690_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_690_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_690_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_690_76.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_690_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_690_83.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_690_86.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\nWhile the documents provide information about Silapathar, they don't mention any area codes or phone numbers associated with it.  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents do not provide any information about the area code for Silapathar. While it mentions that the pincode (postal code) of Silapathar is 787059, there is no reference to an area code such as +91 or 03753."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The area code of Silapathar is given as 787059 which follows the Indian Pincode system, not a standard phone area code.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}